{
    "questions" : [
        {   "sections"      : "※ [1~3] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "35_1_img",
            "option_1"      : "①  ",
            "option_2"      : "②  ",
            "option_3"      : "③  ",
            "option_4"      : "④  ",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Can you take a look at this? I spilled coffee on my clothes.\nMan : Shall we take a look? Well......, it will be clean if you wash it. Until when should I do it for you?\nWoman : Please do it by tomorrow.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  ",
            "score"         : "2",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [1~3] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "35_2_img",
            "option_1"      : "①  ",
            "option_2"      : "②  ",
            "option_3"      : "③  ",
            "option_4"      : "④  ",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : I've been frustrated for a while, but it's good to come up to a high place.\nMan : Isn't it? So I like hiking It makes me feel comfortable when I look at it from the top like this.\nWoman : That's right. We come often now.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  ",
            "score"         : "2",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [1~3] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "35_3_img",
            "option_1"      : "① ",
            "option_2"      : "② ",
            "option_3"      : "③  ",
            "option_4"      : "④  ",
            "detail"        : "\nAs the number of smartphone users increases, the number of mobile shoppers has increased dramatically. It appears that people in their 20s use it the most, followed by teenagers. While many people still shop on their computers, more mobile shoppers are expected in the future.",
            "correctAnswer" : "① ",
            "score"         : "2",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "4. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  기다리게 해서 죄송합니다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  내일은 꼭 나가도록 하겠습니다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  감기에 잘 걸리지 않는 편입니다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  오늘 못 가게 되면 전화 드리겠습니다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : Boss, I don't think I can go out today because I have a cold. I'm sorry.\nWoman : It's okay. By the way, did you go to the hospital? There are many other people, so don't worry and take a good rest.\nMan : I will make sure to go out tomorrow.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  내일은 꼭 나가도록 하겠습니다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "5. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  제시간에 도착해서 다행이에요.",
            "option_2"      : "②  기차가 예정보다 늦게 오겠는데요.",
            "option_3"      : "③  일을 하느라 기차를 놓칠 뻔했어요.",
            "option_4"      : "④  비가 와서 그 시간까지는 힘들겠는데요.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : Welcome, sir. Where do you want me to take you.\nWoman: Seoul Station. By the way, sir, can I get there by 7 o'clock? I have to take the train.\nMan : It must be hard until that time because it's raining.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  비가 와서 그 시간까지는 힘들겠는데요.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "6. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  안 그래도 다 팔렸더라고요.",
            "option_2"      : "②  어제 벌써 하나 사 왔어요.",
            "option_3"      : "③  저도 한번 만들어 보려고요.",
            "option_4"      : "④  저도 가게에 가서 사야겠어요.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : The drinks you make at home are popular these days. The way to make it is simple and easy, so they make a lot.\nMan: I make it myself, so it's better for your health than selling it.\nWoman: I'm going to make it, too.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  저도 한번 만들어 보려고요.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "7. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  거실이 좀 넓으면 좋겠어.",
            "option_2"      : "②  이따가 몇 개 더 갖다 놓을게.",
            "option_3"      : "③  그럼 저쪽으로 옮겨야겠네.",
            "option_4"      : "④  화분이 없어서 허전한 것 같아.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : The living room was so spacious that it looked empty, but it's much better to put a few flower pots like this?\nMan: Yes, but I think it would be a little uncomfortable if there was a big flower pot next to the door.\nWoman: Then I'll have to move over there.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  그럼 저쪽으로 옮겨야겠네.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "8. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  신청서만 쓰면 빌릴 수 있어서 참 편해요.",
            "option_2"      : "②  빌려가는 사람들이 생각보다 적었나 봐요.",
            "option_3"      : "③  우산은 내일 출근하는 길에 갖다 드릴게요.",
            "option_4"      : "④  필요할 때 빌릴 수 있어서 좋았는데 아쉽네요.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Well, it suddenly rained, so can you still borrow an umbrella these days?\nMan : What should I do? The umbrella rental service has been suspended since last month. There are too few people returning umbrellas, so it's hard to continue the service.\nWoman: It was good to be able to borrow it when I needed it, but it's a pity.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  필요할 때 빌릴 수 있어서 좋았는데 아쉽네요.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "9. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  침대의 사진을 찍는다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  침대를 만든 회사에 연락한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  가게로 침대를 가져간다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  중고 가게에 가서 침대를 산다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : I heard you buy furniture from a secondhand store. I'm thinking about selling a bed, what should I do?\nMan : First, take a picture of the bed and post it on the store's website and write down which company it is from. Then the store will contact you.Then do I have to bring the bed?\nMan : No, people from the store will come and take it.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  침대의 사진을 찍는다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "10. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  복사기를 수리할 사람을 찾는다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  복사기의 종류와 가격을 조사한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  구매팀에 복사기 상태를 설명한다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  사무실에서 쓸 복사기를 사러 간다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Team leader, I think we need to buy a new copy machine.\nMan : Why? You can't fix it?\nFemale : Yes, the copier is so old that it's going to cost a lot to fix. Why don't you talk to the purchasing team and buy a new one?\nMan : I do. Then you can tell me the details.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  구매팀에 복사기 상태를 설명한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "11. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  인문학 강의를 신청한다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  남자와 함께 강의를 듣는다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  교재를 사러 서점으로 간다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  홈페이지에서 교재를 확인한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Minsu, are you going to take a humanities class this time?\nMan : I heard it last year. The Lecture is so popular that you will have to apply quickly.\nWoman : Oh, yes. Then we'll have to hurry. By the way, what is the textbook? It wasn't on the homepage.\nMan : Really? I have the book, so I'll bring it to you tomorrow.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  인문학 강의를 신청한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "12. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  현장학습 일정을 짠다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  체험관의 위치를 알아본다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  자연재해를 체험해 본다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  체험관의 프로그램을 확인한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : Mr. Kang, where should we go for this field trip?\nWoman : Well, how about the Safety Education Experience Center? Experiencing natural disasters such as earthquakes will be beneficial to students.\nMan : That would be great. I'll have to find out specifically what kind of programs are there are. I'll check the location, too.\nWoman : I'll find the location for you.\nMan : Really? Thank you, Mr. Kang. Then I should make a detailed schedule.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  체험관의 위치를 알아본다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "13. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  해외 온라인 쇼핑몰은 물건 값이 싸서 세일을 안 한다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  해외 온라인 쇼핑몰 물건은 한국보다 가격이 더 비싸다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  해외 온라인 쇼핑몰에서 물건을 주문하는 방법은 복잡하다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  해외 온라인 쇼핑을 하면 물건을 받을 때까지 오래 기다려야 한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : I heard it's cheap if you buy something at an overseas online shopping mall?\nMan : Yes. It takes a little long, but it's much cheaper. You can buy things that you can't get in Korea.\nWoman : Isn't it complicated to order? I'm thinking of trying it too.\nMan : It wasn't very difficult. It's cheaper if it's on sale, so take a good look at the sale period.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  해외 온라인 쇼핑을 하면 물건을 받을 때까지 오래 기다려야 한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "14. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  공원에서 영화를 상영할 것이다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  영화 촬영 때문에 공원에서 나가야 한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  영화 촬영하는 모습을 사진으로 찍을 수 있다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  동문 주차장에 있는 차를 다른 곳으로 옮겨야 한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : I will give you guidance. After a while, the filming will be held from 4 to 7 pm. If you have parked your car in the east gate parking lot, please move it to another parking lot in the park. Photography is prohibited during filming, so please cooperate.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  동문 주차장에 있는 차를 다른 곳으로 옮겨야 한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "15. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  이 공연은 어른들을 위해 기획되었다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  이 공연에는 어린이들이 무용수로 나온다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  공연 중에 내용 이해를 돕는 노래가 나온다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  이 발레 공연은 이번에 처음 하는 공연이다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : The following is the news of the encore ballet performance that became popular at the end of last year. This performance is a ballet prepared for children by a dance troupe made up of teachers from an art high school. Dancers dress up in animal costumes and dance for children to enjoy. Songs are also added to help children understand. It would be nice to see the whole family together for a holiday outing .",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  공연 중에 내용 이해를 돕는 노래가 나온다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "16. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  열차의 분위기는 현대적이다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  10년 전부터 카페를 운영하였다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  기차역과 열차를 카페로 바꿨다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  카페 손님은 주민들이 대부분이다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Today, we are at Songjeong Station, a train station where there are no trains. Stationmaster, please introduce this place.\nMan : This is a place where trains have not been running for 10 years. So I haven't been using history. A recent suggestion from a resident made a train station and train into an old train-like cafe. The response of the local residents is good, and more tourists come after hearing the word of mouth of the guests who visited this place.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  기차역과 열차를 카페로 바꿨다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [17~20] 다음을 듣고 남자의 중심 생각을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "17. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  장기간 떠나는 여행은 여러 가지 장점이 많다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  시간이 날 때마다 여행을 다니는 것이 좋다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  여행을 오랫동안 다녀오면 다시 취직하기가 힘들다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  여행을 떠나기 전에는 철저한 계획과 준비가 필요하다",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : Hyuna quit her job and is going to travel around the world on a one-year plan. I think it's really amazing.\nWoman : I heard that. But I don't understand why you quit your job and go on a trip. You can travel while working at a company.\nMan : It doesn't last long. I think it's good to go on a long trip at least once because you can take a rest and look back on yourself and make new plans.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  장기간 떠나는 여행은 여러 가지 장점이 많다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [17~20] 다음을 듣고 남자의 중심 생각을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "18. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  운동은 각자의 체력에 맞게 해야 한다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  운동을 주 3회 하면 효과를 볼 수 없다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  자기에게 맞는 운동을 골라서 해야 한다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  스트레스를 받으면 운동을 안 하는 게 좋다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : Then I understand that you will start exercising next Monday. Do you have any more questions?\nWoman : I think I'll only be here about three times a week. Can I see the effects of exercise like that?\nMan : Of course. Three times is enough. It's not good to exercise a lot. Too much exercise is worse for your health because your body is stressed out. It's better not to overdo it and do it moderately.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  운동은 각자의 체력에 맞게 해야 한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [17~20] 다음을 듣고 남자의 중심 생각을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "19. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "① 어렸을 때 재능은 학교에서 발견할 수 있다.",
            "option_2"      : "② 아이들의 방송 출연은 걱정할 문제가 아니다.",
            "option_3"      : "③ 어렸을 때 방송에 출연하면 공부를 할 수 없다.",
            "option_4"      : "④ 아이들과 함께 방송에 출연하면 부작용이 있다.",
            "detail"        : "\nMan : Celebrities often appear on television with their children.\nFemale: Yeah. But are there any side effects on the children?\nMan : I don't think there's anything to worry about because I'm coming out with my parents, not alone. Above all, I think it would be good to be able to discover children's talents early.\nFemale : I'm at the age when I have to go to school, but I don't have time to study because of broadcasting.",
            "correctAnswer" : "② 아이들의 방송 출연은 걱정할 문제가 아니다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [17~20] 다음을 듣고 남자의 중심 생각을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "20. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  전통 한복의 특징을 지키는 것이 중요하다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  화려한 디자인의 한복은 대중화가 어렵다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  전통 한복의 색과 선은 표현하기가 까다롭다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  한복의 대중화를 위해 색과 디자인을 바꿔야 한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nFemale : Kim Young-jae instructor is famous for making traditional Hanbok only. Is there a special reason?\nMan : I think protecting the beauty of traditional hanbok is more important than popularizing hanbok. Modern Hanbok contributed to popularizing Hanbok with colorful colors and practical designs. But the most important elements of hanbok are colors and lines that are not too much. If these unique characteristics are missing, it's not really hanbok.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  전통 한복의 특징을 지키는 것이 중요하다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [21~22] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "21. 남자의 중심 생각으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  학교에서 소개하는 집은 믿을 만한 집이다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  다른 사람과 함께 사는 것은 긍정적인 면도 있다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  여러 사람이 함께 살면 사생활을 보호받지 못한다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  공동생활을 하면 다른 사람의 생활을 존중해야 한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : I couldn't apply because I mistook the dormitory application date, what should I do?\nMan : There's a house that the school introduces, do you want to apply? It's a way to share a deposit with other students and rent a house together, so the deposit burden is low.\nWoman : So we share a house? I think it would be a little uncomfortable to live together in the same house. I'm sure there are a lot of things to care about each other.\nMan : Communal life is better than I thought. Since I use the room alone, I have my own space. Public spaces such as the kitchen and living room are managed together, so it's more comfortable than when you're alone. I feel less lonely because we can rely on each other.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  공동생활을 하면 다른 사람의 생활을 존중해야 한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [21~22] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "22. 들은 내용으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  남자는 혼자 사는 것이 편하다고 생각한다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  학교에서 소개해 주는 집은 보증금을 내야 한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  기숙사 신청 마감일까지 아직 시간이 남아 있다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  학교에서 소개하는 집에는 혼자 쓰는 방이 없다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : I couldn't apply because I mistook the dormitory application date, what should I do?\nMan : There's a house that the school introduces, do you want to apply? It's a way to share a deposit with other students and rent a house together, so the deposit burden is low.\nWoman : So we share a house? I think it would be a little uncomfortable to live together in the same house. I'm sure there are a lot of things to care about each other.\nMan : Communal life is better than I thought. Since I use the room alone, I have my own space. Public spaces such as the kitchen and living room are managed together, so it's more comfortable than when you're alone. I feel less lonely because we can rely on each other.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  기숙사 신청 마감일까지 아직 시간이 남아 있다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [23~24] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "23. 남자의 중심 생각으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  ‘이름 부르기’ 서비스를 제안하고 있다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  ‘이름 부르기’ 서비스의 개선을 요구하고 있다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  ‘이름 부르기’ 서비스의 필요성을 강조하고 있다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  ‘이름 부르기’ 서비스에 대한 반응을 보고하고 있다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Assistant Manager Kim, what is the response of the 'Call Your Name' service?\nMan: I think it's good so far. When the drink I ordered is ready, customers seem to feel friendly because they call out my name, not a vibrating bell, unlike before.\nWoman : So let's wait and see for the time being. But have there been any negative comments reported so far?\nMan : There was an opinion that it was inconvenient to hear the name calling when the store was crowded, but there were no other major complaints.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  ‘이름 부르기’ 서비스에 대한 반응을 보고하고 있다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [25~26] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "24. 들은 내용으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  이 서비스에 대한 고객들의 반응이 좋지 않다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  고객들은 자기 이름이 불리는 것을 불편하게 생각한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  이 서비스 시작 전에는 음료가 준비되면 진동벨로 알렸다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  매장이 복잡할 때는 이름을 부르지 않고 진동벨을 사용한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nWoman : Assistant Manager Kim, what is the response of the 'Call Your Name' service?\nMan: I think it's good so far. When the drink I ordered is ready, customers seem to feel friendly because they call out my name, not a vibrating bell, unlike before.\nWoman : So let's wait and see for the time being. But have there been any negative comments reported so far?\nMan : There was an opinion that it was inconvenient to hear the name calling when the store was crowded, but there were no other major complaints.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  매장이 복잡할 때는 이름을 부르지 않고 진동벨을 사용한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [25~26] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "25. 남자의 중심 생각으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  작품의 가치는 그 재료에 따라 달라진다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  사람들은 작품을 보면서 다양한 의미를 찾는다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  일회용품의 사용 제한은 환경에 관심을 가지게 한다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  환경 문제를 스스로 인식할 수 있도록 해 줘야 한다.",
            "detail"        : "\nFemale : I heard that you make a work of art out of discarded paper. I think there's a reason why you're doing this kind of work.\nMan : We use discarded paper as a material because we want to have a message in the painting. How many people are going to be told, 'Let's not use disposable products' and put it into practice? But more people will realize environmental problems when they see a piece of paper thrown away. And eventually, people who are not interested in the environment will naturally recognize the environmental problem. I think this method has more power than saying let's protect the environment.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  환경 문제를 스스로 인식할 수 있도록 해 줘야 한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [25~26] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "26. 들은 내용으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  이 남자는 환경 문제에 관심이 없다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  이 남자는 작품을 통해 메시지를 전하고 있다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  이 남자는 버려진 일회용품으로 작품을 만든다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  이 남자가 만든 작품에는 특별한 의미가 없다.",
            "detail"        : "\nFemale : I heard that you make a work of art out of discarded paper. I think there's a reason why you're doing this kind of work.\nMan : We use discarded paper as a material because we want to have a message in the painting. How many people are going to be told, 'Let's not use disposable products' and put it into practice? But more people will realize environmental problems when they see a piece of paper thrown away. And eventually, people who are not interested in the environment will naturally recognize the environmental problem. I think this method has more power than saying let's protect the environment.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  이 남자는 작품을 통해 메시지를 전하고 있다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        }
        
    ]
   
}
